<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="convo_start">
        <item>What was the last funny video you saw?</item>
        <item>What do you do to get rid of stress?</item>
        <item>What is something you are obsessed with?</item>
        <item>Who is your favorite entertainer (comedian, musician, actor, etc.)?</item>
        <item>What\'s your favorite way to waste time?</item>
        <item>Do you have any pets? What are their names?</item>
        <item>Where did you go last weekend? What did you do?</item>
        <item>What are you going to do this weekend?</item>
        <item>What is something that is popular now that annoys you?</item>
        <item>What did you do on your last vacation?</item>
        <item>What was the last time you worked incredibly hard?</item>
        <item>Are you very active of do you prefer to just relax in your free time?</item>
        <item>What do you do when you hang out with your friends?</item>
        <item>Do you sleep with a stuffed animal?</item>
        <item>Tell me about your first car.</item>
        <item>Do you drink coffee or tea?</item>
        <item>If you could have any super power, what would it be?</item>
        <item>If you were stranded on a deserted island and you could have only 1 item, what would
            it be?
        </item>
        <item>Do you believe in luck?</item>
        <item>Do you play video games?</item>
        <item>Do you believe people are inherently good?</item>
        <item>How often do you shower?</item>
        <item>What is your favorite board game?</item>
        <item>What is your favorite charity?</item>
        <item>Have you ever gotten a speeding ticket?</item>
        <item>Do you prefer cats or dogs?</item>
        <item>Would you prefer to live in the city or a rural area?</item>
        <item>What is your favorite season?</item>
        <item>Do you speak any other languages?</item>
        <item>Have you ever cried because you were so happy?</item>
        <item>What is the best thing that happened to you during the past week?</item>
        <item>What is the worst thing that happened to you during the past week?</item>
        <item>Do you sing in the shower?</item>
        <item>What is the most valuable thing that you own?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you only had 24 hours left to live?</item>
        <item>Who is your oldest friend? Where did you meet them?</item>

        <item>What\'s the best / worst thing about your work / school?</item>

        <item>If you had intro music, what song would it be? Why?</item>

        <item>What were you really into when you were a kid?</item>

        <item>If you could have any animal as a pet, what animal would you choose?</item>

        <item>What three words best describe you?</item>

        <item>What would be your perfect weekend?</item>

        <item>What do you think of tattoos? Do you have any?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most useful thing you own?</item>

        <item>Have you ever saved an animal\'s life? How about a person\'s life?</item>

        <item>If you opened a business, what kind of business would it be?</item>

        <item>Are you a very organized person?</item>

        <item>Have you ever spoke in front of a large group of people? How did it go?</item>

        <item>What is the strangest dream you have ever had?</item>

        <item>What is a controversial opinion you have?</item>

        <item>Who in your life brings you the most joy?</item>
        <item>Who had the biggest impact on the person you have become?</item>
        <item>What is the most annoying habit someone can have?</item>
        <item>Where is the most beautiful place you have been?</item>
        <item>Where do you spend most of your free time / day?</item>
        <item>Who was your best friend in elementary school?</item>
        <item>How often do you stay up past 3 a.m.?</item>
        <item>What\'s your favorite season? Why?</item>
        <item>Which is more important, a great car or a great house? Why?</item>
        <item>What animal or insect do you wish humans could eradicate?</item>
        <item>Where is the most beautiful place near where you live?</item>
        <item>What do you bring with you everywhere you go?</item>
        <item>How much time do you spend on the internet? What do you usually do?</item>
        <item>What is the most disgusting habit some people have?</item>
        <item>Where and when was the most amazing sunset you have ever seen?</item>
        <item>Which recent news story is the most interesting?</item>
        <item>Where is the worst place you have been stuck for a long time?</item>
        <item>If you had to change your name, what would your new name be?</item>
        <item>What is something that really annoys you but doesn\'t bother most people?</item>
        <item>What word or saying from the past do you think should come back?</item>
        <item>How should success be measured? By that measurement, who is the most successful person
            you know?
        </item>
        <item>What is your guilty pleasure?</item>
        <item>Was there ever an event in your life that defied explanation?</item>
        <item>If you could learn the answer to one question about your future, what would the
            question be?
        </item>
        <item>Has anyone ever saved your life?</item>
        <item>What benefit do you bring to the group when you hang out with friends?</item>
        <item>How often do you curse?</item>
        <item>What trends did you follow when you were younger?</item>
        <item>What do you fear is hiding in the dark?</item>
        <item>What was the best time period of your life? What do you think will be the best time
            period of your entire life?
        </item>
        <item>What do you do to improve your mood when you are in a bad mood?</item>
        <item>What is the silliest fear you have?</item>
        <item>What are some things you want to accomplish before you die?</item>
        <item>What is the best room in your house? Why?</item>
        <item>Who is someone who is popular now that you really like? Why do you like them so
            much?
        </item>
        <item>Where is the best place to take a date?</item>
        <item>What smell brings back great memories?</item>
        <item>How often do you help others? Who do you help? How do you help?</item>
        <item>What are you best at?</item>
        <item>What makes you nervous?</item>
        <item>Who, besides your parents, had the biggest impact on your life?</item>
        <item>What weird or useless talent do you have?</item>
        <item>What are some strange beliefs that some people have?</item>
        <item>Who would be the worst person to be stuck in an elevator with? How about the best
            person to be stuck in an elevator with?
        </item>
        <item>What\'s the funniest TV series you have seen?</item>
        <item>Which TV show do you want your life to be like?</item>
        <item>If you could bring back one TV show that was cancelled, which one would you bring
            back?
        </item>
        <item>How have TV shows changed over the years?</item>
        <item>What\'s the best sitcom past or present?</item>
        <item>What\'s the best show currently on TV?</item>
        <item>What do you think about game shows? Do you have a favorite one?</item>
        <item>What\'s the most underrated or overrated TV show?</item>
        <item>What do you think about reality TV? Why is it so popular?</item>
        <item>Do you like reality TV shows? Why or why not? If so, which ones?</item>
        <item>What will be the future of TV shows?</item>
        <item>What was the best birthday wish or gift you\'ve ever received?</item>
        <item>How often do you binge watch shows?</item>
        <item>What cartoons did you watch as a child?</item>
        <item>What\'s are some of your Pavlovian responses?</item>
        <item>Where did you grow up?</item>
        <item>Do you have any pets?</item>
        <item>Do you have any siblings?</item>
        <item>Do you know what your your name means?</item>
        <item>What type of phone do you have?</item>
        <item>What did you do this past weekend?</item>
        <item>What are your plans for this weekend?</item>
        <item>What do you like to do in your spare time?</item>
        <item>What is the first thing you do when you wake up?</item>
        <item>What is the last thing you do before you go to sleep?</item>
        <item>What is your middle name?</item>
        <item>What was the last thing you purchased?</item>
        <item>What is your favorite holiday?</item>
        <item>What is your favorite day of the week?</item>
        <item>If you could meet anyone in history, who would it be?</item>
        <item>What do you like to do to relax?</item>
        <item>Are you a saver or a spender?</item>
        <item>Do you play any instruments?</item>
        <item>What was the last movie you watched? How was it?</item>

        <item>Do you prefer to watch movies in the theater or in the comfort of your own home?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the worst movie you have seen recently?</item>

        <item>What\'s the strangest movie you have ever seen?</item>

        <item>What is the most overrated movie?</item>

        <item>What\'s your favorite genre of movie?</item>

        <item>What movie scene choked you up the most?</item>

        <item>Do you like documentaries? Why / why not?</item>

        <item>When was the last time you went to a movie theater?</item>

        <item>Do movies have the same power as books to change the world?</item>

        <item>Which do you prefer? Books or movies?</item>

        <item>Do you like horror movies? Why or why not?</item>
        <item>What song always puts you in a good mood?</item>

        <item>Which do you prefer, popular music or relatively unknown music?</item>

        <item>What was the last song you listened to?</item>

        <item>What is your favorite movie soundtrack?</item>

        <item>Are there any songs that always bring a tear to your eye?</item>

        <item>Do you like going to concerts? Why or why not? What was the last concert you went
            to?
        </item>

        <item>Who was the first band or musician you were really into? Do you still like them?
        </item>

        <item>Records, tapes, CDs, MP3s. Which did you grow up with? What is good and bad about
            each?
        </item>

        <item>What bands or types of music do you listen to when you exercise?</item>

        <item>Do you like classical music?</item>

        <item>What\'s the best way to discover new music?</item>

        <item>How has technology changed the music industry?</item>
        <item>What are the three best apps on your phone?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most addictive mobile game you have played?</item>

        <item>An app mysteriously appears on your phone that does something amazing. What does it
            do?
        </item>

        <item>How many apps do you have on your phone?</item>

        <item>What is the most annoying app you have tried?</item>

        <item>Which app seemed like magic the first time you used it?</item>

        <item>What is the strangest app you have heard of or tried?</item>

        <item>Which app has helped society the most? Which one has hurt society the most?</item>

        <item>What is the most useful app on your phone?</item>

        <item>What apps have changed your life a lot?</item>

        <item>What do app makers do that really annoys you?</item>
        <item>How often do you check your phone?</item>

        <item>Do you always have to have the latest phone?</item>

        <item>What was your first smart phone? How did you feel when you got it?</item>

        <item>What is the most annoying thing about your phone?</item>

        <item>What kind of case do you have for your phone? Why did you choose it?</item>

        <item>Do you text more or call more? Why?</item>

        <item>What will phones be like in 10 years?</item>

        <item>Do you experience phantom vibration? (Feeling your phone vibrate even though it
            didn\'t.)
        </item>

        <item>How do you feel if you accidentally leave your phone at home?</item>

        <item>What do you wish your phone could do?</item>
        <item>Have you traveled to any different countries? Which ones?</item>

        <item>Where is the most relaxing place you have been?</item>

        <item>Where is the most awe inspiring place you have been?</item>

        <item>Do you prefer traveling alone or with a group?</item>

        <item>What do you think of tour group packages?</item>

        <item>Talk about some of the interesting people you have met while traveling.</item>

        <item>Where would you like to travel next?</item>

        <item>What was the most over hyped place you\'ve traveled to?</item>

        <item>What\'s the best way to travel? (Plane, car, train, etc.)</item>

        <item>What\'s the best thing about traveling? How about the worst thing?</item>

        <item>How do you think traveling to a lot of different countries changes a person?</item>

        <item>What is the longest plane trip you have taken?</item>

        <item>What do you think of stay-cations? (Vacationing and seeing tourist attractions where
            you live.)
        </item>

        <item>Do you prefer to go off the beaten path when you travel?</item>

        <item>Where do you get your recommendations for what to do and where to stay when you
            travel?
        </item>

        <item>What is the worst hotel you have stayed at? How about the best hotel?</item>
        <item>Do you care about fashion? What style of clothes do you usually wear?</item>

        <item>What is the best pair of shoes you have ever owned? Why were they so good?</item>

        <item>What is your favorite shirt?</item>

        <item>What is the most embarrassing piece of clothing you own?</item>

        <item>Does fashion help society in any way?</item>

        <item>What is a fashion trend you are really glad went away?</item>

        <item>Who do you think has the biggest impact on fashion trends: actors and actresses,
            musicians, fashion designers, or consumers?
        </item>

        <item>What old trend is coming back these days?</item>

        <item>If you didn\'t care at all what people thought of you, what clothes would you wear?
        </item>

        <item>What is the most comfortable piece of clothing you own?</item>

        <item>How do clothes change how the opposite sex views a person?</item>
        <item>What is the craziest, most outrageous thing you want to achieve?</item>

        <item>What are some goals you have already achieved?</item>

        <item>What personal goals do you have?</item>

        <item>What do you hope to achieve in your professional life?</item>

        <item>Have your parents influenced what goals you have?</item>

        <item>Do you usually achieve goals you set? Why or why not?</item>

        <item>What is the best way to stay motivated and complete goals?</item>

        <item>What are some goals you have failed to accomplish?</item>

        <item>When do you want to retire? What do you want to do when you retire?</item>

        <item>What are your goals for the next two years?</item>

        <item>How have your goals changed over your life?</item>

        <item>How much do you plan for the future?</item>

        <item>How do you plan to make the world a better place?</item>
        <item>What is your favorite food?</item>

        <item>Do you like spicy food? Why or why not? What is the spiciest thing you have ever
            eaten?
        </item>

        <item>What foods do you absolutely hate?</item>

        <item>What food do you know you shouldn\'t eat but can\'t help yourself?</item>

        <item>Does government have a place in regulating food? To what extent should government
            regulate food?
        </item>

        <item>When was the last time you had a food fight?</item>

        <item>What do you get every time you go grocery shopping?</item>

        <item>If your life was a meal, what would kind of meal would it be?</item>

        <item>What do you think of buffets?</item>

        <item>What would you want your last meal to be if you were on death row?</item>

        <item>What food looks disgusting but tastes delicious?</item>

        <item>When people make mistakes about food (especially foreign food) do you feel the need to
            correct them? (i.e. sushi / sashimi or stromboli / calzone)
        </item>
        <item>Time freezes for everyone but you for one day. What do you do?</item>

        <item>If you could call up anyone in the world and have a one hour conversation, who would
            you call?
        </item>

        <item>You have to relive one day of your life forever. Which day do you choose?</item>

        <item>If your mind was an island, what would it look like?</item>

        <item>What flavor of ice cream do you wish existed?</item>

        <item>What does your own personal hell look like? How about your own personal heaven?</item>

        <item>A portal to another world opens in front of you. You don\'t know how long it will stay
            open or if you\'ll be able to get back after you go through. What do you do?
        </item>

        <item>If you had a personal mascot, what would your mascot be?</item>

        <item>You find a remote that can rewind, fast forward, stop and start time. What do you do
            with it?
        </item>

        <item>If you were a king / queen, what would your throne look like?</item>

        <item>If you were on the run from the police for a crime you didn\'t commit, where would you
            go?
        </item>
        <item>When you are old, what do you think children will ask you to tell stories about?
        </item>

        <item>If you could switch two movie characters, what switch would lead to the most
            inappropriate movies?
        </item>

        <item>What animal would be cutest if scaled down to the size of a cat?</item>

        <item>What inanimate object would be the most annoying if it played loud upbeat music while
            being used?
        </item>

        <item>When did something start out badly for you but in the end, it was great?</item>

        <item>What weird food combinations do you really enjoy?</item>

        <item>How would your country change if everyone, regardless of age, could vote?</item>

        <item>What are some red flags to watch out for in daily life?</item>

        <item>If your job gave you a surprise three day paid break to rest and recuperate, what
            would you do with those three days?
        </item>

        <item>Where do you get your news?</item>

        <item>What movie can you watch over and over without ever getting tired of?</item>

        <item>What\'s wrong but sounds right?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most epic way you\'ve seen someone quit or be fired?</item>

        <item>If you couldn\'t be convicted of any one type of crime, what criminal charge would you
            like to be immune to?
        </item>

        <item>What social stigma does society need to get over?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most creative use of emojis you\'ve ever seen?</item>

        <item>What\'s something that will always be in fashion, no matter how much time passes?
        </item>

        <item>What actors or actresses play the same character in almost every movie or show they
            do?
        </item>

        <item>In the past people were buried with the items they would need in the afterlife, what
            would you want buried with you so you could use it in the afterlife?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the best / worst practical joke that you\'ve played on someone or that was
            played on you?
        </item>

        <item>Who do you go out of your way to be nice to?</item>

        <item>Where do you get most of the decorations for your home?</item>

        <item>What food have you never eaten but would really like to try?</item>

        <item>What food is delicious but a pain to eat?</item>

        <item>Who was your craziest / most interesting teacher</item>

        <item>What "old person" things do you do?</item>

        <item>What was the last photo you took?</item>

        <item>What is the most amazing slow motion video you\'ve seen?</item>

        <item>Where are some unusual places you\'ve been?</item>

        <item>Which celebrity do you think is the most down to earth?</item>

        <item>What would be the worst thing to hear as you are going under anesthesia before heart
            surgery?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the spiciest thing you\'ve ever eaten?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most expensive thing you\'ve broken?</item>

        <item>What obstacles would be included in the World\'s most amazing obstacle course?</item>

        <item>What makes you roll your eyes every time you hear it?</item>

        <item>What do you think you are much better at than you actually are?</item>

        <item>Should kidneys be able to be bought and sold?</item>

        <item>When was the last time you got to tell someone "I told you so."?</item>

        <item>What would a world populated by clones of you be like?</item>

        <item>What riddles do you know?</item>

        <item>What\'s your cure for hiccups?</item>

        <item>What invention doesn\'t get a lot of love, but has greatly improved the world?</item>

        <item>What\'s something you really resent paying for?</item>

        <item>Do you think that aliens exist?</item>

        <item>What are you currently worried about?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most interesting building you\'ve ever seen or been in?</item>

        <item>What mythical creature do you wish actually existed?</item>

        <item>What are your most important rules when going on a date?</item>

        <item>How do you judge a person?</item>

        <item>If someone narrated your life, who would you want to be the narrator?</item>

        <item>What was the most unsettling film you\'ve seen?</item>

        <item>What unethical experiment would have the biggest positive impact on society as a
            whole?
        </item>

        <item>When was the last time you were snooping, and found something you wish you hadn\'t?
        </item>

        <item>Which celebrity or band has the worst fan base?</item>

        <item>What are you interested in that most people aren\'t?</item>

        <item>If you were given a PhD degree, but had no more knowledge of the subject of the degree
            besides what you have now, what degree would you want to be given to you?
        </item>

        <item>What smartphone feature would you actually be excited for a company to implement?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s something people don\'t worry about but really should?</item>

        <item>What movie quotes do you use on a regular basis?</item>

        <item>Do you think that children born today will have better or worse lives than their
            parents?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the funniest joke you know by heart?</item>

        <item>When was the last time you felt you had a new lease on life?</item>

        <item>What\'s the funniest actual name you\'ve heard of someone having?</item>

        <item>Which charity or charitable cause is most deserving of money?</item>

        <item>What TV show character would it be the most fun to change places with for a week?
        </item>

        <item>What was cool when you were young but isn\'t cool now?</item>

        <item>If you were moving to another country, but could only pack one carry-on sized bag,
            what would you pack?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the most ironic thing you\'ve seen happen?</item>

        <item>If magic was real, what spell would you try to learn first?</item>

        <item>If you were a ghost and could possess people, what would you make them do?</item>

        <item>What goal do you think humanity is not focused enough on achieving?</item>

        <item>What problem are you currently grappling with?</item>

        <item>What character in a movie could have been great, but the actor they cast didn\'t fit
            the role?
        </item>

        <item>What game have you spent the most hours playing?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most comfortable bed or chair you\'ve ever been in?</item>

        <item>What\'s the craziest conversation you\'ve overheard?</item>

        <item>What\'s the hardest you\'ve ever worked?</item>

        <item>What movie, picture, or video always makes you laugh no matter how often you watch
            it?
        </item>

        <item>What artist or band do you always recommend when someone asks for a music
            recommendation?
        </item>

        <item>If you could have an all-expenses paid trip to see any famous world monument, which
            monument would you choose?
        </item>

        <item>If animals could talk, which animal would be the most annoying?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most addicted to a game you\'ve ever been?</item>
        <item>What\'s the coldest you\'ve ever been?</item>

        <item>Which protagonist from a book or movie would make the worst roommate?</item>

        <item>Do you eat food that\'s past its expiration date if it still smells and looks fine?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the most ridiculous thing you have bought?</item>

        <item>What\'s the funniest comedy skit you\'ve seen?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most depressing meal you\'ve eaten?</item>

        <item>What tips or tricks have you picked up from your job / jobs?</item>

        <item>What outdoor activity haven\'t you tried, but would like to?</item>

        <item>What songs hit you with a wave of nostalgia every time you hear them?</item>

        <item>What\'s the worst backhanded compliment you could give someone?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most interesting documentary you\'ve ever watched?</item>

        <item>What was the last song you sung along to?</item>

        <item>What\'s the funniest thing you\'ve done or had happen while your mind was wandering?
        </item>

        <item>What app can you not believe someone hasn\'t made yet?</item>

        <item>When was the last time you face palmed?</item>

        <item>If you were given five million dollars to open a small museum, what kind of museum
            would you create?
        </item>

        <item>Which of your vices or bad habits would be the hardest to give up?</item>

        <item>What really needs to be modernized?</item>

        <item>When was the last time you slept more than nine hours?</item>

        <item>How comfortable are you speaking in front of large groups of people?</item>

        <item>What\'s your worst example of procrastination?</item>

        <item>Who has zero filter between their brain and mouth?</item>

        <item>What was your most recent lie?</item>

        <item>When was the last time you immediately regretted something you said?</item>

        <item>What would be the best thing you could reasonably expect to find in a cave?</item>

        <item>What did you think was going to be amazing but turned out to be horrible?</item>

        <item>What bit of trivia do you know that is very interesting but also very useless?</item>

        <item>What\'s the silliest thing you\'ve seen someone get upset about?</item>

        <item>What animal or plant do you think should be renamed?</item>

        <item>What was the best thing that happened to you today?</item>

        <item>What languages do you wish you could speak?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most pleasant sounding accent?</item>

        <item>What\'s something that everyone, absolutely everyone, in the entire world can agree
            on?
        </item>

        <item>What country is the strangest?</item>

        <item>What\'s the funniest word in the English language?</item>

        <item>What\'s some insider knowledge that only people in your line of work have?</item>

        <item>Who do you wish you could get back into contact with?</item>

        <item>How do you make yourself sleep when you can\'t seem to get to sleep?</item>

        <item>If people receive a purple heart for bravery, what would other color hearts
            represent?
        </item>

        <item>What are some of the best vacations you\'ve had?</item>

        <item>If there was a book of commandments for the modern world, what would some of the rules
            be?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the craziest video you\'ve ever seen?</item>

        <item>What\'s your "Back in my day, we-"?</item>

        <item>If you could know the truth behind every conspiracy, but you would instantly die if
            you hinted that you knew the truth, would you want to know?
        </item>

        <item>What animal would be the most terrifying if it could speak?</item>

        <item>What\'s the worst hairstyle you\'ve ever had?</item>

        <item>What habit do you have now that you wish you started much earlier?</item>

        <item>If you were given one thousand acres of land that you didn\'t need to pay taxes on but
            couldn\'t sell, what would you do with it?
        </item>

        <item>What about the opposite sex confuses you the most?</item>

        <item>When was the last time you yelled at someone?</item>

        <item>What\'s the opposite of a koala?</item>

        <item>What kinds of things do you like to cook or are good at cooking?</item>

        <item>What life skills are rarely taught but extremely useful?</item>

        <item>What movie universe would be the worst to live out your life in?</item>

        <item>If you could hack into any one computer, which computer would you choose?</item>

        <item>Who do you feel like you know even though you\'ve never met them?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most ridiculous animal on the planet?</item>

        <item>What\'s the worst thing you\'ve eaten out of politeness?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most historic thing that has happened in your lifetime?</item>

        <item>What happens in your country regularly that people in most countries would find
            strange or bizarre?
        </item>

        <item>What has been blown way out of proportion?</item>

        <item>When was a time you acted nonchalant but were going crazy inside?</item>

        <item>What\'s about to get much better?</item>

        <item>What are some clever examples of misdirection you\'ve seen?</item>

        <item>What\'s your funniest story involving a car?</item>

        <item>What would be the click-bait titles of some popular movies?</item>

        <item>If you built a themed hotel, what would the theme be and what would the rooms look
            like?
        </item>

        <item>What scientific discovery would change the course of humanity overnight if it was
            discovered?
        </item>

        <item>Do you think that humans will ever be able to live together in harmony?</item>

        <item>What would your perfect bar look like?</item>

        <item>What\'s the scariest nonhorror movie?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most amazing true story you\'ve heard?</item>

        <item>What\'s the grossest food that you just can\'t get enough of?</item>

        <item>What brand are you most loyal to?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most awkward thing that happens to you on a regular basis?</item>

        <item>If you had to disappear and start a whole new life, what would you want your new life
            to look like?
        </item>

        <item>What movie or book do you know the most quotes from?</item>

        <item>What was one of the most interesting concerts you\'ve been to?</item>

        <item>Where are you not welcome anymore?</item>

        <item>What do you think could be done to improve the media?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most recent show you\'ve binge watched?</item>

        <item>What\'s the worst movie trope?</item>

        <item>What\'s a common experience for many people that you\'ve never experienced?</item>

        <item>What are some misconceptions about your hobby?</item>

        <item>What\'s the smartest thing you\'ve seen an animal do?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most annoying noise?</item>

        <item>What\'s your haunted house story?</item>

        <item>What did you Google last?</item>

        <item>What\'s the dumbest thing someone has argued with you about?</item>

        <item>If money and practicality weren\'t a problem, what would be the most interesting way to
            get around town?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the longest rabbit hole you\'ve been down?</item>

        <item>What\'s the saddest scene in a movie or TV series?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most frustrating product you own?</item>

        <item>What inconsequential super power would you like to have?</item>

        <item>What qualities do all your friends have in common?</item>

        <item>What odd smell do you really enjoy?</item>

        <item>What\'s the coolest animal you\'ve seen in the wild?</item>

        <item>What\'s the best lesson you\'ve learned from a work of fiction?</item>

        <item>What food do you crave most often?</item>

        <item>Who in your life has the best / worst luck?</item>

        <item>What fashion trend makes you cringe or laugh every time you see it?</item>

        <item>What\'s your best story of you or someone else trying to be sneaky and failing
            miserably?
        </item>

        <item>Which apocalyptic dystopia do you think is most likely?</item>

        <item>If you had a HUD that showed three stats about any person you looked at, what three
            stats would you want it to show?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the funniest thing you\'ve seen a kid do?</item>

        <item>What\'s your secret talent?</item>

        <item>What\'s the best way you or someone you know has gotten out of a ticket / trouble with
            the law?
        </item>

        <item>Tear gas makes people cry and laughing gas makes people giggle, what other kinds of
            gases do you wish existed?
        </item>
        <item>What\'s the most beautiful beach you\'ve been to?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most anxiety inducing thing you do on a regular basis?</item>

        <item>What\'s something that everyone agrees we should change, but somehow it never
            changes?
        </item>

        <item>What trend are you tired of?</item>

        <item>What\'s incredibly cheap and you would pay way more for?</item>

        <item>What\'s your grossest bug story?</item>

        <item>What would the adult version of an ice-cream truck sell and what song would it play?
        </item>

        <item>What company do you despise?</item>

        <item>When was the most inappropriate time you busted out in laughter?</item>

        <item>What would be an accurate tag line for each month?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most overrated product out on the market?</item>

        <item>What word do you always misspell?</item>

        <item>What naps are the most satisfying?</item>

        <item>What\'s the weirdest thing you\'ve found lying on the ground / side of the road?</item>

        <item>What\'s the funniest TV show you\'ve ever seen?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most embarrassing story from your childhood?</item>

        <item>What animal is the most majestic?</item>

        <item>What\'s something that everyone knows is true, but we don\'t like to admit it?</item>

        <item>What\'s the weirdest text or email you\'ve gotten?</item>

        <item>What always cheers you up when you think about it?</item>

        <item>What sport could you play the longest in a televised game, without anyone discovering
            you aren\'t a professional athlete?
        </item>

        <item>If you could talk to animals and they would understand you, but you couldn\'t
            understand them, what would you do with that power?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the most boring sport, and what would you do to make it more exciting?</item>

        <item>What\'s the creepiest tech out there?</item>

        <item>Who did you use to look up to, but they screwed up and you lost faith in them?</item>

        <item>What\'s fine in small numbers but terrifying in large numbers?</item>

        <item>Do you like things to be carefully planned or do you prefer to just go with the
            flow?
        </item>

        <item>What animal would you most like to eat?</item>

        <item>What fictional characters have you had a crush on over the years?</item>

        <item>What would the box with all your hopes and dreams inside look like?</item>

        <item>What was the worst shopping experience you\'ve ever had?</item>

        <item>What story you\'ve heard has stayed with you and always disturbs you every time you
            think about it?
        </item>

        <item>What was the most important appointment or deadline you missed?</item>

        <item>If you were a clown themed super hero, what powers would you have?</item>

        <item>If you could airdrop anything you want, worth two million dollars or less, anywhere
            you want, what would you airdrop and where would you airdrop it?
        </item>

        <item>If you lived in a virtual reality world of your own creation, what would it look
            like?
        </item>

        <item>What escalated very quickly?</item>

        <item>What two things are terrible when separate but great when you put them together?
        </item>

        <item>What did you believe for way too long as a child?</item>

        <item>What big event do you think will happen soon that most people aren\'t expecting?</item>

        <item>What still makes you cringe when you think back on it?</item>

        <item>What current trend makes no sense to you?</item>

        <item>If you owned a restaurant, what kind of food would it serve?</item>

        <item>Which celebrity is the most likely to have a collection of canes that are just for
            show?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the weirdest crush you\'ve had?</item>

        <item>What do a lot of people have very strong opinions about, even though they know very
            little about it?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s your go to casino game?</item>

        <item>An epic feast is held in your honor, What\'s on the table?</item>

        <item>What\'s your favorite holiday movie?</item>

        <item>Who is the most manipulative person you\'ve ever met?</item>

        <item>Who is the most creative person you know?</item>

        <item>What\'s the funniest pick up line you\'ve heard?</item>

        <item>What seemingly innocent question makes you think "It\'s a trap!"?</item>

        <item>How ambitious are you?</item>

        <item>What did you like / dislike about where you grew up?</item>

        <item>What elements of pop culture will be forever tied in your mind to your childhood?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s your good luck charm?</item>

        <item>What\'s legal now, but probably won\'t be in 25 years?</item>

        <item>Would you want the ability to hear the thoughts of people near you if you couldn\'t
            turn the ability off?
        </item>

        <item>When was the last time you stayed up through the entire night?</item>

        <item>What\'s something that people think makes them look cool, but actually has the opposite
            effect?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the oldest thing you own?</item>

        <item>What has someone borrowed but never given back?</item>

        <item>Where is the best place you\'ve been for taking walks?</item>

        <item>If cartoon physics suddenly replaced real physics, what are some things you would want
            to try?
        </item>

        <item>What from the present will withstand the test of time?</item>

        <item>Who in your life is the worst at using technology?</item>

        <item>What\'s the weirdest conversation you\'ve eavesdropped on?</item>

        <item>What just around the corner tech are you eager to get your hands on?</item>

        <item>What was the darkest movie you\'ve ever seen?</item>

        <item>What do you do when you hear something fall in the middle of the night while you are
            in bed?
        </item>

        <item>What outfit could you put together from clothes you own to get the most laughs?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most disgusting sounding word in the English language?</item>

        <item>What was ruined because it became popular?</item>

        <item>What outdated slang do you use on a regular basis?</item>

        <item>What was the biggest realization you had about yourself?</item>

        <item>What\'s your best example of easy come, easy go?</item>

        <item>What small change greatly improves a person\'s appearance?</item>

        <item>What topic could you spend hours talking about?</item>

        <item>What happens regularly that would horrify a person from 100 years ago?</item>

        <item>What do a lot of people hope will happen but is just not going to happen?</item>

        <item>What\'s the weirdest thing that has happened to you while working at your job?</item>

        <item>What questions would you like to ask a time traveler from 200 years in the future?
        </item>

        <item>Which way should toilet paper hang, over or under?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most physically painful thing you\'ve ever experienced?</item>

        <item>What horror story do you have from a job you\'ve had?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most rage inducing game you\'ve ever played?</item>

        <item>What\'s the biggest overreaction you\'ve ever seen?</item>

        <item>What are some of the most common misconceptions?</item>

        <item>What job doesn\'t exist now but will exist in the future?</item>
        <item>What awful movie do you love?</item>

        <item>What normally delicious food gets ruined when you wrap it in a tortilla?</item>

        <item>What\'s your best example of fake it till you make it?</item>

        <item>What were you completely certain of until you found out you were wrong?</item>

        <item>What\'s something commonly done that gets progressively weirder the more you think
            about it?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s the cutest thing you can imagine? Something so cute it\'s almost painful.</item>

        <item>If you were given unlimited resources, how would you lure the worst of humanity into
            one stadium at the same time?
        </item>

        <item>What do you think about when you hear the word "classy"?</item>

        <item>What near future predictions do you have?</item>

        <item>What do you need help with most often?</item>

        <item>What piece of "art" would you create if you had to pretend to be an artist and submit
            something to a gallery?
        </item>

        <item>What do you do to make the world a better place?</item>

        <item>What\'s the best and worst thing about the country you are from?</item>

        <item>If you were in charge renaming things so that their names would be more accurate, what
            names would you come up with?
        </item>

        <item>What\'s better broken than whole?</item>

        <item>What values are most important to you?</item>

        <item>What\'s the best sandwich you\'ve ever had?</item>

        <item>What\'s the worst thing you ate from a fast food restaurant?</item>

        <item>What\'s something that I don\'t know?</item>

        <item>What profession doesn\'t get enough credit or respect?</item>

        <item>What memory of yours feels real but is most likely false?</item>

        <item>What\'s your "and then it got worse" story?</item>

        <item>What was the most amazing physical feat you\'ve managed to pull off?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most annoying thing about the social media platform you use most often?
        </item>

        <item>If you were hired to show tourists what life is really like where you live, what would
            you show them / have them do?
        </item>

        <item>What would be the most unsettling thing to keep occasionally finding around your
            house?
        </item>

        <item>What nicknames do you have for people in your life?</item>

        <item>What does the opposite sex do that you wish that you could do, but it\'s not
            anatomically feasible or it\'s socially frowned upon?
        </item>

        <item>How much do you plan / prepare for the future?</item>

        <item>What do you hate most and love most about your car?</item>

        <item>What weird potato chip flavor that doesn\'t exist would you like to try?</item>

        <item>What\'s the silliest thing you\'ve convinced someone of?</item>

        <item>How much do you think names affect the outcomes of people\'s lives?</item>

        <item>What product or service is way more expensive than it needs to be?</item>

        <item>What\'s the shadiest thing you\'ve seen someone do?</item>

        <item>What was the last situation where some weird stuff went down and everyone acted like
            it was normal, and you weren\'t sure if you were crazy or everyone around you was crazy?
        </item>

        <item>What did you eat so much of that now you hate it?</item>

        <item>What are some of the dumbest lyrics you\'ve heard in a song?</item>

        <item>Where\'s the line between soup and cereal?</item>

        <item>What word do you always mispronounce?</item>

        <item>What do you think you do better than 90% of people?</item>

        <item>What would be the worst food to be liquefied and drunk through a straw?</item>

        <item>What\'s the weirdest thing about modern life that people just accept as normal?</item>

        <item>How much of your body would you cybernetically enhance if you could?</item>

        <item>If you wanted to slowly drive a roommate insane using only notes, what kind of notes
            would you leave around the house?
        </item>

        <item>If you had a giraffe that you needed to hide, where would you hide it?</item>

        <item>What\'s the clumsiest thing you\'ve done?</item>

        <item>What songs do you only know the chorus to?</item>

        <item>Think of a brand, now what would an honest slogan for that brand be?</item>

        <item>What\'s something common from your childhood that will seem strange to future
            generations?
        </item>
        <item>What\'s the most amazing place in nature you\'ve been?</item>

        <item>What\'s quickly becoming obsolete?</item>

        <item>Where is the most uncomfortable place you have ever slept?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most annoying animal you\'ve encountered?</item>

        <item>What\'s your best example of correlation not equaling causation?</item>

        <item>In what situations, do you wish you could throw down a smoke bomb and disappear?
        </item>

        <item>When was the last time you were hopelessly lost?</item>

        <item>What songs do you feel compelled to sing along with when you hear them, even if you
            don\'t totally know all the words?
        </item>

        <item>What product do you wish a company would make a "smart" version of?</item>

        <item>What two films would you like to combine into one?</item>

        <item>As a child, what did you think would be awesome about being an adult, but isn\'t as
            awesome as you thought it would be?
        </item>

        <item>When\'s censorship warranted?</item>

        <item>What\'s the most boring super hero you can come up with?</item>

        <item>What would be some of the downsides of certain superpowers?</item>

        <item>What word is a lot of fun to say?</item>

        <item>What current trend do you hope will go on for a long time?</item>

        <item>What actors or actresses can\'t play a different character because they played their
            most famous character too well?
        </item>

        <item>Where\'s your go to restaurant for amazing food?</item>

        <item>What\'s something that all your friends agree on?</item>

        <item>What\'s your best story from a wedding?</item>


    </array>
</resources>
